Guide to the Cornell University Glee Club Records, 1884-2014
Cornell University Glee Club Records, 1884-2014
- Series IV. Managerial Papers
  - Subseries C. Thomas B. Tracy Years
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1954 Also contains newspaper clippings, arrangements for appearance on Perry Como show. (Box 7)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence (continued), 1954 Also contains newspaper clippings, numerous photographs of the group, individual members, Thomas Tracy, Perry Como and other performers. (Box 7)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1955 Also contains newspaper clippings. (Box 7)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1956 Also contains papers regarding disassociation of Cayuga's Waiters. (Box 7)
  - Subseries D. Tracy and Sokol Years
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1957 (Box 7)
  - Subseries E. Thomas A. Sokol Years
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence (continued), 1958 Also contains tour program. (Box 8)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence (continued), 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence (I), 1959 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence (II), 1959 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Toledo Visit, 1959 (Box 8)
    - Pittsburgh Visit, 1959 (Box 8)
    - Indianapolis and Lima Visit, 1959 (Box 8)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1960 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs, papers regarding Soviet Union tour. (Box 8)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence (continued), 1960 Contains papers regarding Soviet Union tour. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence (continued), 1960 Contains papers regarding Soviet Union tour. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1960-1961 Also contains concert programs, papers regarding reorganization as part of university. (Box 8)
    - Managerial File: Russian Tour Vol. 2, 1960-1961 (Box 8)
    - Russian Tour Notes, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1961-1962 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs, 1961 Constitution, performance with Nadia Boulanger. (Box 9)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence Vol. 1, 1962-1963 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs, Eugene Ormandy performance. (Box 9)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence Vol. 2, 1962-1963 Also contains information about new recording, finances, photographs of album covers. (Box 9)
    - Managerial Forms and Correspondence Vol. 3, 1962-1963 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs. (Box 9)
    - England Tour, June 1963 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs. (Box 9)
    - Managerial Records Vol. 1, 1963-1964 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs, second issuing of Constitution, Perkins inauguration, John F. Kennedy Memorial Convocation. (Box 9)
    - Managerial Records Vol. 2, 1963-1964 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs, Robert Palmer world premiere. (Box 9)
    - Managerial Records Vol. 3, 1963-1964 Also contains newspaper clippings, information about Songs of Cornell recording. (Box 9)
    - Managerial Records Vol. 4, 1963-1964 Also contains newspaper clippings, information about Songs of Cornell recording. (Box 10)
    - Managerial Papers, 1964-1965 Also contains newspapers clippings, concert programs, Cornell Centennial, correspondence with Erich Kunzel. (Box 10)
    - Accounts and Expenses, 1964-1965 (Box 10)
    - President's Report, 1964-1965 (Box 10)
    - Spring Tour, 1965 Baltimore, Bergen City, Bethlehem, Boston, Buffalo, Darlen, Goucher College, Hanover, Harrisburg, Hartford, Lackawanna, Nassau County, New Haven, Newton College, Philadelphia, Poughkeepsie, Union City, Washington, D.C., Westchester, Wilmington, Wilton High School. (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous Papers, 1965 Brief history of CUGC, roster, constitution. (Box 10)
    - Press Book, 1965 Newspaper clippings, magazine articles. (Box 10)
    - Publicity Book, 1965 Newspaper clippings, magazine articles, concert programs. (Box 10)
    - Managerial Papers, 1965-1966 Also contains concert programs, Cornell Latin American Year activities. (Box 10)
    - Pre-Tour Correspondence for Far East Tour, 1966 Also contains extensive correspondence with U.S. Government and Selective Service, letter from Senator Robert F. Kennedy dated January 4, 1966. (Box 10)
    - Far East Tour Orientation Book (Vol. I), 1966 Travel brochures, tour booklets, and miscellany about Japan, Ceylon, Malaysia, Singapore, Hong Kong. (Box 10)
    - Far East Tour Orientation Book (Vol. II), 1966 Travel brochures, tour booklets, and miscellany about Korea and Japan. (Box 10)
    - Far East Tour News Releases for Each Member, 1966 Brief biography of each participant on tour. (Box 10)
    - CUGC World Tour - The Daily Journal of Richard H. R. Bull, 1966 (Box 10)
    - A Report of the Far East Tour of the CUGC by Thomas A. Sokol, 1966 Also contains Alumni News article. (Box 10)
    - A Report of the Far East Tour of the CUGC by Thomas A. Sokol, 1966 Also contains Alumni News article, poster, and publicity from tour. (Box 10)
    - President's Report, 1965-1966 Also contains performance and repertoire lists from Far East Tour. (Box 11)
    - Accounts and Expenses, 1965-1966 (Box 11)
    - Managerial Papers (Book I), 1966-1967 Also contains newspaper clippings, preliminary plans for tour to Canada. (Box 11)
    - Managerial Papers (Book II), 1966-1967 Also contains concert programs. (Box 11)
    - Managerial Papers (Book III), 1966-1967 Also contains concert programs, photograph of marquee at InterLakes Finance, 127 West State St. (Box 11)
    - Budget, 1966-1967 (Box 11)
    - President's Report - Centennial Year, 1967-1968 Also contains centennial program. (Box 11)
    - Managerial Papers (Book I), 1967-1968 Also contains newspaper clipping, concert programs, centennial material. (Box 11)
    - Managerial Papers (Book II), 1967-1968 Also contains concert programs. (Box 11)
    - Presidential Reports/Papers, Advisory Council, 1967-1969 (Box 11)
    - President's Report, 1968-1969 (Box 11)
    - Managerial Records (Book I), 1968-1969 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs. (Box 11)
    - Managerial Records (Book II), 1968-1969 Also contains newspaper clippings. (Box 11)
    - Proposed South America Tour, 1969-1970 Also contains letters from Secretary of State William P. Rogers, Sol M. Linowitz, and Robert W. Purcell. (Box 11)
    - President's Report, 1969-1970 Also contains informatinon formation of the Glee Club Association, first newsletter. (Box 12)
    - Financial Records, 1969-1970 (Box 12)
    - Managerial Records, 1969-1970 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs. (Box 12)
    - Association Papers, 1969-1970 Also contains first two issues of newsletter. (Box 12)
    - Association, Advisory Council, Presidential Papers, 1969-1970 Also contains Association tax exempt papers. (Box 12)
    - Association, Advisory Council, Presidential Papers, 1970-1971 Also contains information regarding the Gail Singleton audition debacle, letters from Nicholas H. Noyes, letter and sheet music for "The Sea, The Sky, and The Mountains" by R. Alex Anderson. (Box 12)
    - President's Report, 1970-1971 Also contains information regarding the Gail Singleton audition debacle, newsletters #3 and #4. (Box 12)
    - Financial Papers, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Managerial Records - German Tour 1970 (I), 1969-1970 Also contains concert programs. (Box 12)
    - Managerial Records - German Tour 1970 (II), 1969-1970 Also contains newspaper clippings. (Box 12)
    - German Tour News Clippings, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Managerial Papers (Book I), 1970-1971 Also contains newspaper clippings and concert programs. (Box 12)
    - Managerial Papers (Book II), 1970-1971 Also contains newspaper clippings and concert programs. (Box 12)
    - Spring "Junket" Book One (Managerial Papers), 1971 Also contains newspaper clippings and concert programs. (Box 12)
    - Spring "Junket" Book Two (Managerial Papers), 1971 Also contains newspaper clippings and concert programs. (Box 12)
    - President's Report, 1971-1972 (Box 13)
    - Managerial Papers - Eastern European Tour - General Index and Tour Report, 1971-1972 (Box 13)
    - Managerial Papers (Book I), 1971-1972 Also contains newspaper clippings, recruiting booklet, "RIP Hangovers" paper. (Box 13)
    - Managerial Papers (Book II), 1971-1972 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs. (Box 13)
    - Managerial Papers (Book III), 1971-1972 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs. (Box 13)
    - Managerial Papers - Eastern European Tour Papers (Book IV), 1971-1972 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs. (Box 13)
    - Managerial Papers - Eastern European Tour Papers (Book V), 1971-1972 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs. (Box 13)
    - Managerial Papers - Eastern European Tour Papers (Book VI), 1971-1972 Also contains correspondence with composer Franz Biebl, correspondence regarding George Gull's stolen camera/film and its return. (Box 13)
    - Managerial Papers - Eastern European Tour Papers (Book VII), 1971-1972 Also contains newspapers clippings, concert programs. (Box 13)
    - Financial Records, 1971-1972 (Box 13)
    - President and Manager Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous, 1972-1973 Press book, concert programs, letter about amendment to Constitution regarding gender, newsletters #7 and #8. (Box 13)
    - Managerial Papers (Book I, Part I), 1972-1973 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs. (Box 14)
    - Managerial Papers (Book I, Part II), 1972-1973 Also contains newspaper clippings. (Box 14)
    - Managerial Papers (Book II, Part I), 1972-1973 Also contains newspaper clippings, discussion of moving accounts out of Music Department, press regarding amendment to the Constitution removing the word "male." (Box 14)
    - Managerial Papers (Book II, Part II), 1972-1973 Also contains newspaper clippings, press book rewrite. (Box 14)
    - Presidential Correspondence, Advisory Council, Alumni Association/Correspondence, Annual Reports, 1972-1973 Also contains newspaper clippings, newsletters #6-8, endowment drive correspondence, "Song of the Classes" verses (grad student, tax payers, politics), clippings regarding death of Thomas Tracy and memorial endowment, Thomas Swart memorial (non-CUGC alumnus whose death notice directed money to the CUGC). (Box 14)
    - Financial Papers, 1972-1973 (Box 14)
    - Southeastern Tour, 1973 Also contains newspaper clippings. (Box 14)
    - Southeastern Tour (Book #2), January 1973 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs. (Box 14)
    - Southeastern Tour (Book #3), January 1973 Also contains concert programs, "The Hill" parody, newsletter #8. (Box 14)
    - Managerial Papers, 1973-1974 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs. (Box 14)
    - President's and Manager's Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 14)
    - Aborted West Coast Tour - Intended for Winter 1975 1973-1974 (Box 14)
    - Senior Week and Homecoming, 1974 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs. (Box 14)
    - Managerial Records, 1974-1975 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs. (Box 15)
    - Managerial Records (continued), 1974-1975 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs (Commencement, Sage Chapel Centennial). (Box 15)
    - Managerial Records (continued), 1974-1975 Also contains newspaper clippings. (Box 15)
    - Southern States Tour, January 1975 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs. (Box 15)
    - President's Report, 1974-1975 (Box 15)
    - Ithaca Concerts (Homecoming 1975, Senior Week 1976), 1975-1976 Also contains concert program. (Box 15)
    - Northeastern Tour (Book I), January 1976 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs. (Box 15)
    - Managerial Papers (Juceam Books, Book I), May 1975-May 1977 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs, information on hiring secretaries, arrangements for canceled Hawaii tour. (Box 15)
    - Managerial Papers (Juceam Books, Book II), May 1975-May 1977 Also contains president's and manager's reports. (Box 15)
    - Managerial Papers (Juceam Books, Book III), May 1975-May 1977 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs, list of Dudley award recipients from 1964-1976 and detailed information about the origin and purpose of the award. (Box 16)
    - Finances, 1975-1976 (Box 16)
    - Annual Report (President's Report and Manager's Report), 1975-1976 (Box 16)
    - Annual Report (President's Report), 1976-1977 (Box 16)
    - Managerial Papers, 1977-1978 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs. (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous Papers, 1977-1978 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs. (Box 16)
    - Chattanooga, TN Concert Papers, January 1978 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - President's Books, 1977-1978 Also contains endowment drive, solicitations, and Association correspondence. (Box 16)
    - Annual Report, 1977-1978 Also contains newsletters #17 and #18. (Box 16)
    - Campaign Drive Letters, 1977-1979 (Box 16)
    - Ithaca Concerts, 1978-1979 Also contains newspapers articles, concert programs. (Box 16)
    - Annual Report, 1978-1979 (Box 16)
    - England Tour (Book 1), January 1979 (Box 16)
    - England Tour (Book 2), January 1979 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert poster. (Box 16)
    - England Tour (Book 3), January 1979 Also contains concert programs. (Box 16)
    - England Tour (Book 4), January 1979 Also contains fundraising information, tour rosters for past international tours from Mexico 1954 on. (Box 17)
    - Mexican Tour program, 1954 (Box 17)
    - Ithaca Concerts, 1979-1980 Also contains newspaper clippings, concert programs. (Box 17)
    - Annual Report, 1979-1980 Also contains newsletters #21 and #22. (Box 17)
    - England Tour (Book I), 1982 Also contains concert programs, travel brochures. (Box 17)
    - England Tour (Book II), 1982 Also contains concert program, travel brochures. (Box 17)
    - Long Range Plan, 1986 (Box 17)
  - F. Miscellaneous Papers
    - Intercollegiate Musical Council (IMC), 1956-1970 (Box 17)
    - Cornell Women's Glee Club Managerial Forms and Correspondence, 1958-1960 (Box 17)
    - Constitution and Preliminary Papers, 1960-1962 Contains papers pertaining to the reorganization under University control and creation of the Advisory Council. (Box 17)
    - Presidential Papers, 1957-1962 (Box 17)
    - Presidential Reports/Papers, Advisory Council, 1962-1967 (Box 17)
    - Magazine Publicity, 1963-1966 Booklet of London arrangements, 1963; Cornell Alumni News, Sep. 1963; Cornell Countryman, May 1964; Cornell Alumni News, Nov. 1966. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Endowment Fund, 1963-1973 (Box 17)
    - International Tour Resources, 1969 Listing of Corporations With Major Divisions Abroad. (Box 17)
    - Association Books - Finances, 1969-1980 (Box 17)
    - "Blending Voices: A Scrapbook of Stories and Pictures from a Group Singer", by Jack Brophy (Box 29, Folder 1)
      Available online: http://hdl.handle.net/1813/44653
- Series V. Publications
  - Songs of Cornell, Published by B. F. Lent., 1900 (Box 3)
  - Songs of Cornell, negative proof sheets for book., 1988 (Box 18)
- Series VI. The Hangovers
  - The Hangovers Tuxedo Junction, 1981; SR-9845, 9848 (Box 31)
  - The Hangovers Cheers, 1986; SR-9846-9847 (Box 31)
  - FT XXIII World Stage Productions, V-9141-9142 (Box 29)
  - The Principles of a Hang: A Docu-Drama of the FTXXI Weekend, V-9143-9144 (Box 29)
  - FT XXI World Stage Productions, V-9145-9146 (Box 29)
  - The Hangovers: Fall Tonic XX, V-9147-9148 (Box 29)
  - The Hangovers Present: Fall Tonic XVIII, November 17, 1997; V-9149-9150 (Box 29)
  - The Hangovers Fall Tonic XXVI, November 9, 1996; tr-10921-10922 (Box 29)
  - Fall Tonic XXIV, November 8 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Happy Hour, April 30 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Fall Tonic XXVI, November 12, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Happy Hour XII, May 6, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Happy Hour XIV, May 4, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Happy Hour XVI, May 1 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Happy Hour XI, May 1 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Fall Tonic XXIX, November 1, 2008 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Fall Tonic XXXI, November 13 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Happy Hour XXII, May 7 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Fall Tonic XXXII, November 11 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Happy Hour XX, May 3 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Fall Tonic XXXIII, November 3, 2012 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, program (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Happy Hour X, May 2 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Fall Tonic XIII, November 14, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Fall Tonic XV, November 12, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Fall Tonic, November 7, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Fall Tonic XI, November 10 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Fall Tonic XIII, November 16, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Fall Tonic, November 1 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Fall Tonic IX, November 12 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Fall Tonic, October 23 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - "Blending Voices: A Scrapbook of Stories and Pictures from a Group Singer", by Jack Brophy (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Series VII. Other materials
  - Subseries A. Printed material
    - Newspapers from Asia Tour, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Newspapers, 1960s-1980s (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Newspapers, 1990s (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Newspapers, 2000s (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Newspapers, 2010s (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Mandolin Club, Clarence Parker, ca. 1910 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Songs from the Hill, 1998 (Box 21)
      A History of the Cornell University Glee Club by Michael Slon
    - Song of Cornell (Box 21)
      Signed by Tom Sokol, with letter to and from Della-Marie Meisinger
    - Songs of Cornell ISBN, Illustrations, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Songs of Cornell memos, correspondence, schedules, proofreading, versions, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Songs from the Hill 1st draft, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 3-5)
    - Songs from the Hill final draft, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 6-8)
    - Songs from the Hill proofs, plates, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Songs from the Hill master corrected proofs, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 10-12)
    - Songs from the Hill proofs, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 13-14)
    - Songs from the Hill proofs, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 15-16)
    - Songs from the Hill unbound copy (Box 23)
    - Ticket for Glee, Banjo & Mandolin Clubs concert at New Wieting Theatre, Syracuse, NY, Dec. 26, 1907 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Candidates for Membership in Cornell Glee, Banjo and Mandolin Clubs index cards, 1936, 1937, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Program for Cornell Reunions Weekend Events, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Artwork advertising theremin concert at Bailey Hall, March 22, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Blank certificate/shingle for Cornell University Orchestra (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper Ad and Ticket Stub for concert at St. Mary's Hall, Henley, England, Jul. 10, 1895 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Armistead Taylor Waight Glee, Banjo and Mandolin Club shingle certificate., 1906 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Eisteddfod Gerddorol Ryngwladol Llangollen international musical Eisteddfod poster and appreciation certificate, 2012 (Box 18)
  - Subseries B. Posters and Fliers
    - UCLA: California Tour, January 15, 2011 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Senior Week Concert, May 29, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Sage Chapel Christmas Vespers, December 7-8, 2008 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Sage Chapel Christmas Vespers, December 4-5, 2011 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Senior Week Concert, May 27, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Bach's Mass in B Minor, April 16, 2011 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Senior Week Concert, May 28, 2011 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Autumn Auditions Poster, Unknown (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - The Vintage Years: Memorial Room, February 28, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Homecoming Concert, September 23, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Music from the German Tour, April 23, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Karel Husa: Bailey Hall, March 15, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Matches poster with similar year ambiguity. Clarifies Fall Concert, October 24, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Senior Week Concert, May 29, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club @ Sage Chapel: Year debatable, May 4, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Homecoming Concert, September 17, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Bruckner's Mass in E Minor, March 6, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Bruckner's Mass in E Minor, May 1, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Homecoming Concert, September 27, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Senior Week Concert, May 23, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Senior Week Concert, May 25, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Karel Husa: Music for Prague 1968, May 3, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Homecoming ("Fall") Concert, October 14, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Senior Week Concert, May 25, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Uppsala University Chamber Choir United States Tour at Sage Chapel, April 21, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Smith College Glee Club in Ithaca Concert Series at Sage Chapel, November 23, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Homecoming ("Fall") Concert, October 27, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Glee Club at Elmira College, December 2, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Cornell and Holyoke Glee Clubs: Mozart Mass in C Minor at Abbey Chapel, March 8, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Homecoming Concert, October 10, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Homecoming Concert, October 16, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Munich: Germany, January 27, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Christmas Concert: Statler, December 5, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Return From Tour Concert: Midwest Tour, January 24, 2012 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Return From Tour Concert: Southeast Tour, January 22, 2013 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Haas Seven Soundscapes on the Unfinished Fragments of Mozart's Requiem, April 25, 2014 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Senior Week Concert, May 24, 2014 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Senior Week Concert, May 29, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Savage Club Show ft. Cornell Glee Club, June 11, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Nuremberg: Germany, January 29, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - White Plains High School, New York, April 1, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Chicago Concert: Midwest Tour, January 7, 2012 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Homecoming Concert, September 22, 2012 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Senior Week Concert, May 26, 2012 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Senior Week Concert, May 26, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Brahms Ein deutsches Requiem: GC and Ch Shanghai Oriental Art Center, March 22, 2008 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Easter Evensong Concert: Tsuen Wan Concert Hall, March 23, 2008 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Senior Weekend Concert program, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - St. James Hall Cornell program, 1895 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - St. Louis Picture, 1916 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Missa Solemnis, Music For Prague 1968: Karel Husa and Syracuse Symphony, March 10, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Senior Week Concert, May 28, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Segunda: Brazil, March 22, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Brahms Ein deutsches Requiem: GC and Ch Sage Chapel, February 4, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - St. John Passion: Bailey Hall, April 17, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Probably Fall Concert: Year debatable, October 24, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Benefit Concert for the Ken Kunken Fund, June 6, 1971 (Map-case 1, Folder 1)
    - The Philadelphia Orchestra and Cornell University Glee Club and Chorus under Eugene Ormandy (Map-case 1)
    - Cornell Glee Club in Eastern Europe, June 7, 1972 (Map-case 1)
    - Cornell Glee Club in Eastern Europe, January 5, 1972 (Map-case 1)
    - Glee Club Tour Celebration concert "Auf Wiedersehen", June 7, 1972 (Map-case 1)
    - Glee Club and Chorus perform Carmina Burana with Karel Husa, conductor, March 22, 1970 (Map-case 1)
    - Kings Lynn Festival, July 1, 1982 (Map-case 1)